<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Quizzes</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="fetchQuestionsService">quiz-school/mobileData/request.php?request=QuizStart&amp;module=handShake&amp;title=does-your-crush-like-you-girls-only_1</string>
    <string name="serviceBaseUrl">http://www.proprofs.com/</string>
    <string name="app_id">1089558781080623</string>
    <string name="send_to">Share via</string>


    <string name="spinner_title">Select Category</string>
    <string name="prompts">Select</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior" translatable="false">android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="pri">These Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy define the conditions under which you may use the www.proprofs.com website (the "ProProfs Website") or the ProProfs Quiz Maker mobile app (the "Application") and are an agreement between you and Batia Infotech ("ProProfs"). By using the ProProfs Website, application or the services provided therein, you agree to be bound by the terms of these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy, as well as any other rules, guidelines and additional terms referenced herein, which are hereby incorporated herein by reference (collectively, "Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy"). If you are unwilling to be bound by these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy, you should not access or use the ProProfs Website, application or the services.</string>
 <string name="pris">These Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy are subject to change by ProProfs at any time, effective when we post a notice on the ProProfs Website, effective immediately, and your use of the ProProfs Website, application or services after such posting will constitute acceptance by you of such changes. It is your responsibility to review these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy for any changes each time you visit the ProProfs Website or use the application or services.</string>
    <string name="priss">ProProfs provides services for users and members to create content such as quizzes, polls, surveys, Q&amp;A, forum threads, flashcards, brain games, blogs, wiki pages as well as resources to study for popular exams such IT certification exams, SAT exam, GRE, GMAT and other exams (the "Services"). You can share this content with other users or members by linking to this content or by using our provided widgets &amp; API for this purpose in specific sections. Additionally, members can comment on and view such content on the ProProfs Website or application.</string>
    <string name="prisss">Your use of the Services is expressly limited to non-commercial, personal and private use only. Any use for commercial gain is expressly prohibited.</string>
    <string name="privac">You acknowledge and agree that from time to time the Services may be inaccessible or inoperable for any reason, including without limitation: (a) equipment malfunctions (b) periodic maintenance procedures or repairs which ProProfs may undertake from time to time or (c) causes beyond the reasonable control of ProProfs or which are not reasonably foreseeable by ProProfs.</string>
    <string name="privaci">You may engage in conferences and chats, download and upload files and otherwise use the Services as permitted by these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy and applicable law. Files that you upload, public messages that you send and your activity in conferences and chats are subject to review, modification and deletion without notice by ProProfs. Files available on the ProProfs Website or application may be subject to posted limitations on usage, reproduction and/or dissemination, and you are responsible for adhering to such limitations if you download them. Any copyright, trademark and other proprietary notices may not be removed from any copies you download or share.</string>

    <string name="pri1">By using our Service or the ProProfs Website or application, you warrant and represent that:
(a) All quizzes, polls, games, surveys, training, content, questions, information, data, text, software, music, sound, photographs, images, video, quiz or polls or any other type of responses, messages or other materials that you upload to the ProProfs Website or application ("Content) are your original works of authorship, and that, if you are uploading the image of any third party, you have obtained the right to use his or her likeness on the ProProfs Website or application, and
(b) By using the ProProfs Website or application and the Services, you may be exposed to Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortuous, defamatory, libelous, vulgar, obscene, offensive, indecent, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable, and you agree and consent to that exposure.
You are solely responsible for your interactions with other members on the ProProfs Website or application. As such, you should not give out any personally identifiable information such as your last name, personal email addresses, username or password to ProProfs.com or application or third-party websites/services, instant messenger addresses, personal URLs, telephone numbers and physical addresses to other members.
Additionally, you should not give out any financial information or transmit electronically or physically any money to other members.
You are solely responsible for your interactions with other members on the ProProfs Website or application. As such, you should not give out any personally identifiable information such as your last name, personal email addresses, username or password to ProProfs.com or application or third-party websites/services, instant messenger addresses, personal URLs, telephone numbers and physical addresses to other members. Additionally, you should not give out any financial information or transmit electronically or physically any money to other membersYou acknowledge and agree that ProProfs has no responsibility or obligations to you in the event that you choose to meet or interact with other users or members of the ProProfs Website or application. Meeting strangers has inherent risks, and you solely assume all such risks if you choose to meet any third party with whom you are introduced on the ProProfs Website or application.

You acknowledge and understand that ProProfs does not (a) in any way screen or inquire into the backgrounds of our members or attempt to verify the statements of our members, or (b) make any representations or warranties as to the conduct of members with any current or future members.
</string>
    <string name="reg">Registration is not required to use the ProProfs Website or application, however, some of our Services (e.g. creating quizzes, polls, flashcards, games, surveys, blogs, forum threads) require you to register as a member before you will be able to access such Services. Upon completing the registration process, ProProfs will provide you with an account that provides you with the personal, non-transferable and non-exclusive right to access and use the Services and the ProProfs Website or application subject to the terms and conditions of these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy. Additionally, during registration you can, at your discretion, authorize ProProfs to send email messages on your behalf to invite your friends to the Service and upload a picture or new content (article, quiz, poll, flashcard, survey, comment etc) in video, photo or text format to add to the site. Registered users shall be referred to as "Members".


    </string>
<string name="reg1">You agree to provide us with the following personal information during registration:</string>
    <string name="reg2">"Email address\n
Username\n
Password\n
Gender\n
Date of Birth\n
Country of residence\n
State/Province/n
City\n
Zip Code and\n
Credit card / Payment details if subscribing to paid services or making a purchase"
</string>
    <string name="reg3">You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your email address and password that you designate during registration. You agree to immediately notify ProProfs of any unauthorized use of your email address, screen name or password or any other security breach and you agree to exit from your account at the end of each session, especially if you are using public computers and networks. Additionally, you should be careful when inputting your email address and password in public settings, so others are not able to view this information. ProProfs will not be liable for any damage or loss due to your failure to comply with this provision.

</string>
    <string name="reg4">You represent and warrant to ProProfs that: (a) you have the power and authority to be bound to and comply with these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy and to perform your obligations under the Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy (b) you will comply with these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy (c) if you choose to register, you have provided or will provide accurate and complete information during the registration process and (d) you own or otherwise control the necessary rights or have the necessary consents to upload or create any content, including but not limited to messages, emails, photographs, text, reviews, testimonials, images or video, that you provide through the Services ("User Submissions").</string>
   <string name="reg5">We reserve the right to (a) terminate any Member registration, with or without prior notice, for any reason, or (b) to remove, suspend or disable any Member\'s access to all or any portion of the Services or the ProProfs Website or application, with or without prior notice, for any reason. In addition, you may terminate your Member registration at any time. Upon termination, you will have no further rights or privileges to use the Services. The terms and conditions of those sections set forth in the Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy labeled "Description of Services: Use of Services", "Prohibited Items and Activities", "Collection of Information", "Use of Information", "Intellectual Property," "Third Party Websites and Advertising", "User Submissions", "Disclaimer of Warranties", "Limitation of Liability" and "Miscellaneous" shall survive the termination of your Member Registration.</string>
   <string name="user1">Members are solely responsible for their User Submissions and all materials they transmit to other members. Members are not allowed to post or transmit to other members any material listed in the "Prohibited Items and Activities" section set forth below. If you provide information to us or other members that subsequently becomes inaccurate, misleading or false, you agree to update your profile promptly to remove such information. ProProfs may review and delete User Submissions that, in the sole discretion of ProProfs, violate these Terms of Service &amp; Privacy Policy, including any such material that might be offensive, illegal or may violate the rights, harm or threaten the safety of other Members.</string>
<string name="user2">You retain all of your ownership rights in your Content submissions. However, by posting User Content to public areas of the ProProfs Website or application, you warrant and represent that you have the right to grant to ProProfs, and you hereby grant to ProProfs, a non-exclusive, irrevocable, sublicensable, worldwide, perpetual, fully paid-up license to copy, reproduce, use, perform, display, adapt, modify, distribute, and create derivative works from such User Submissions. For the avoidance of doubt, this license shall permit ProProfs to use User Submissions for our own marketing purposes, which may include publication and distribution of such User Submissions on third party websites other than the ProProfs Website or application and on third party websites or other media distribution (television, movies, radio, print, outdoor, etc.) not owned or controlled by ProProfs. You further represent and warrant that public posting and use of your User Submissions by ProProfs will not infringe or violate the rights of any third party (see Copyright Dispute Policy). Additionally, your use of the ProProfs Website or application and the Services, including but not limited to the User Submissions you post on the ProProfs Website or application, will be in accordance with any and all applicable laws and regulations.</string>
<string name="elib">The ProProfs Website or application is intended to serve a general audience. Some public portions of the site may not be suitable for children under eighteen (18) years of age.
</string>
    <string name="action_share">Share</string>
    <string name="prob">You expressly agree that you are solely responsible for any and all acts and omissions that occur under your registration and you agree not to engage in any unacceptable uses of the Services, which include, without limitation, use of the Services to do any of the following:</string>
<string name="prob1">Register for the ProProfs Website or application and the Services if you have not acknowledged reading and agreed to abide by these Terms of Service
&amp;\nPrivacy Policy.\nInterfere, disrupt or attempt to gain unauthorized access to other accounts on the ProProfs Website, application or any other computer network.\nUse the ProProfs Website, application or the Services in connection with any commercial endeavors.\nPost your personal information such as last name, email addresses, instant messaging addresses, personal URLs, physical addresses\nand phone numbers in any publicly viewable areas of the ProProfs Website.\nPost or give out any financial information or transmit electronically or physically any money to other Members.\nCreate user accounts by automated means or under fraudulent or false pretenses.\nCreate or transmit unsolicited electronic communications such as spam to Members or promote any products or services.\nSubmit or upload any type of material that is unlawful, harmful, hateful, threatening, abusive, harassing, defamatory, offensive, obscene,pornographic, lewd, lascivious, or otherwise objectionable, as determined by ProProfs.\nSubmit or upload any content for which you do not own all applicable rights or that infringes the proprietary rights of other parties.\nSubmit, engage in or upload any type of competitions or content that can cause physical or mental harm to the participants or visitors to the\nProProfs Website.\n
Harass, threaten or intentionally embarrass or cause harm or distress to another person or group.\n
Collect and publish any information about any of our Members.\n
Adapt, modify or reverse engineer any portion of the Services or the ProProfs Website.\n
Use any spider, robot, retrieval application, or any other device to retrieve any portion of the ProProfs Website.\n
Reformat any of the pages that are part of the ProProfs Website.\n
Disseminate, store or transmit viruses, worms, trojan horses or other malicious code or program.\nEncourage conduct that would constitute a criminal or civil offense.







</string>
</resources>

